teamseer.com 2013-05-03

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Policy

### By using this website you accept the terms of this privacy statement, the copyright statement and the terms and conditions on this website.

### Our commitment to privacy

This privacy statement explains how we (TeamSeer) collect information from you via the website or in any manner expressly described in the privacy statement and how this information is then used. By you (or customer) we mean your company or organisation. When you provide us with your personal data in the manner described, you consent to the processing of all such personal data as set out in the privacy statement. Please read this privacy statement carefully and revisit this page from time to time to review any changes that we may have made. If you have any questions or comments about how we handle your personal information, please contact us. You may also use these contacts to tell us about any concerns you may have about our privacy statement. We have registered as a data controller (in our registered company name of TeamSeer Limited) in line with the United Kingdom Data Protection Act, 1998. Our registration number is Z9369614.

### Giving information for other people

For UK based companies, your company must be registered as a data controller in line with the United Kingdom Data Protection Act, 1998. If you are processing data in order to fulfil your statutory obligations (e.g. to record absence under statutory sick pay regulations), consent from employees is not necessary, and the ICO guidance also makes it clear that consent is not required where you process data in order to determine whether an employee is capable of performing their duties, to make reasonable adjustments to their duties, to fulfill health and safety obligations etc, or to pay health related benefits.

In other countries similar laws are likely to apply, and you are responsible for making sure that you comply with relevant legislation.

### Protecting your personal information

We have security measures in place to make sure any personal information we collect is secure. Your account is password protected and all information including your password is on a secure server, which only a limited number of employees and sub-contractors can access. All parties with access to your information are subject to confidentiality obligations. If you think someone else knows your password, or is using it, tell us immediately and change your password using the admin area of the site.

### Information Security on Transmission

One a client has logged in, all information is transmitted via industry-standard encryption (SSL). However any transmission may in theory be intercepted and decrypted. By using the site you accept that you use the website at your own risk.

### Information Security on your own PCs

TeamSeer does use cookies. Cookies are used (a) to carry out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network (by storing a temporary ‘session’ cookie), and (b) for the provision of the service requested by the subscriber (by storing temporary cookies that facilitate the experience of using TeamSeer). This in accordance with Paragraph 4, Regulation 6 of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (Amendment) Regulations Act 2011.

Depending on the user’s internet settings the web pages visited may be cached on their computer. It is up to customers to determine an appropriate policy to deal with this.

### Access to Data

Each class of user data has its own set of access rights. These determine who can see, edit and update the data in the system. Users are assigned access privileges by the system administrator (usually the HR manager).

### Email Use

Part of the functionality of the system involves sending emails, for example to request a holiday approval.

### Audit Trail

Each change to time-related data (booking holidays, etc) is entered in an audit log. This log is maintained for the benefit of system administrators.

### TeamSeer Access to Data

From time to time you may request assistance from TeamSeer support that requires access to user data. By contacting us and asking for assistance you are deemed to authorise us to do this.

### Data Backup

All data is backed up daily to a secure, remote backup site.

### Statistics Gathering by TeamSeer

From time to time TeamSeer may use the data provided by you to undertake statistical analyses, such as absenteeism rates or system usage patterns. Such analyses will be done across a wide sample of customers and will not be published in a manner that is attributable to any one customer.

### Data Transfer

We may also give your information to third parties who may take over part or all of the TeamSeer business in the future, but only for the purposes outlined in this privacy statement.

### Keeping you informed

We will use your information to send you regular updates about: our services and materials; additions to the website; and specific activities such as customer feedback surveys and competitions.

If you do not wish to receive this information please contact us.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask for a copy of all the information we hold about you (we will charge you a small fee for this) and to correct any inaccuracies. To obtain a copy of this information, please contact us. You can amend your details on the website by logging in to the site.

### Links

Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites and we advise you to read the privacy statement of every website that collects personal information from you.

### Paying for TeamSeer

When sign up online for a subscription with TeamSeer, you will be asked for your credit card details by our secure payment provider. TeamSeer does not know or store your credit card or debit card details.

Last updated: 24 January 2012
